

# Senior Back-end Developer

Budapest, Hungary

+36-70-77-66-703

zoltan.holoda@gmail.com in

Ad astra per asperas

github.com/holodazoltan

zoltan-holoda

# WHO AM I?

I am a professional Java programmer more than 10 years. I am hard-worker, enthustistics, motivated, precise co-worker, who likes the be a part of a team. At the bigger company I like the athmosphere and easy to find the right people to learn from. At smaller company I like bigger responsibility and challenges.





## **EXPERIENCE**

2018 - 2020 Senoir Back-end developer

Code and Soda

Developed custom java based web e-commercial software back-end, create new machine learning based recommenders.

Java-Spring / e-commerce / Machine Learning

2015 - 2018 Senoir Back-end developer

**EU Edge** 

Developed custom java based web e-commercial software back-end.

Java-JEE / e-commerce

2014 – 2015 Junior Back-end developer

Atoll Technology

Developed greenfield Java based speedcams software VEDA to store and manage driver's misdemeanor

Java-JEE / OracleDB

2009 – 2014 Junior Back-end developer

Ericsson Hungary

Developed java based O&M software to manage radio and core network (software, hadware, license management). Knowledge transfer to Hyderabad, India for 2 months.

Java-JEE / Scrum

#### **EDUCATION**

2006 - 2011 **Bachelor of Arts** 

**Budapest University of Technology and Economics** 

I studied at Management and Business Administration Faculty with Enterprise resource planning Speciality. The title of my Masters Thesis is ONE (SAP) introduction at Ericsson Hungary.

2002 – 2009 **Master's Degree** 

**Budapest University of Technology and Economics** 

I studied at Electrical Engineering and Informatics Faculty with Internet and Infocommunication appliances Speciality. The title of my Masters Thesis is Analysis of binary encoding fault-tolerant quantum network.

### LANGUAGES

**HOBBIES** 

#### **NON PROFIT**

**Hungarian** - native **Engish** - proficient **German** - rudimentary I like to walk in the countryside with my family and friends, play soccer, tennis, skiing and cycling. If I have same spare time, I grab a book. I always charity to noble cases like education or environment. Besides, I help to collect waste or help out a friend with fixing an IT issue.